<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
		<rss version="2.0">
			<channel>
				<title><![CDATA[Tip &amp; Tricks for Core Sockets]]></title> 
				
				<description><![CDATA[Tip &amp; Tricks for Core Sockets]]></description> 
				<copyright>2007</copyright>
				<language>en-us</language> 
				<lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2007 03:02:54 EDT</lastBuildDate> 
				<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs> 
				<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Using Ordinal Step]]></title> 
				<category>Developer.cfm</category>
				<category>Sockets.cfm</category>
				<category>116_toolbuilder</category>
				
				<description><![CDATA[By enabling ordinal step in socket tool builder you create a hidden ordinal field you can easily and dynamically change.  Then in your SQL statement you can order by ordinal to display your records in their desired assortment.]]></description> 
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 03:45:11 EDT</pubDate> 
				<guid>100022_Core_Tip</guid>
			</item> 
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Versioning is good]]></title> 
				<category>Developer.cfm</category>
				<category>116_toolbuilder</category>
				
				<description><![CDATA[It is usually good practice to either use versioning or create an active flag so that you can prevent a record from displaying on the site without having to completely delete it from the database.]]></description> 
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2007 12:50:06 EDT</pubDate> 
				<guid>100025_Core_Tip</guid>
			</item> 
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Find Records Fast]]></title> 
				<category>Sockets.cfm</category>
				<category>100_formEnvironment</category>
				
				<description><![CDATA[You can search for records on the socket listing screen by choosing any of the fields in the drop down in the upper right corner of the page and typing in your search criteria in the blank field.]]></description> 
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 05:06:52 EDT</pubDate> 
				<guid>100026_Core_Tip</guid>
			</item> 
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Setting up css styles for my data driven display]]></title> 
				<category>Developer.cfm</category>
				<category>104_displayhandler</category>
				
				<description><![CDATA[Here at DP, we try to use css inheritance to our advantage by using an identifying outer container (ie: whitepaperItem) and inner generic ids and classes (ie: abstract, body) so that we can set generic sitewide styles in site.css an, if needed, overriding styles using inheritance.  For example, you could have .abstract{font-size:12px;} in site.css to apply to all abstracts and .whitepaperItem .abstract{font-size:10px;} to apply only to whitepaper abstracts.]]></description> 
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2007 12:13:43 EDT</pubDate> 
				<guid>100042_Core_Tip</guid>
			</item> 
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[How do I insert a PDF into body content?]]></title> 
				<category>Content.cfm</category>
				<category>Sockets.cfm</category>
				<category>103_page</category>
				<category>109_contentobject</category>
				
				<description><![CDATA[Here are the steps to place the PDF into body content:

1. Upload the PDF to File Manager
2. Copy the Friendly Path/URL line (in File Manager click on the icon to the left of the file that resembles a globe with a link below it) 
3. Then in the Socket field (the "Abstract" or "Body" field in a Socket) or Content Element highlight the text you wish to link the PDF to and select the Insert/Edit Link icon (in the bottom left of the Wysiwyg the icon is the same you used to copy the Friendly Path/URL) and then paste the Friendly Path/URL you copied in File Manager.]]></description> 
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 03:34:07 EDT</pubDate> 
				<guid>100044_Core_Tip</guid>
			</item> 
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[In File Manager what is the difference between Add an Image and Add a File?]]></title> 
				<category>Content.cfm</category>
				<category>Sockets.cfm</category>
				<category>115_filemanager</category>
				
				<description><![CDATA[Nothing.  Both of these icons are used to upload new documents or images to BoomSocket.  Uploading these documents or images is just step number one, after they have been uploaded they then need to be placed into the content.]]></description> 
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 04:28:33 EDT</pubDate> 
				<guid>100045_Core_Tip</guid>
			</item> 
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[What are all of the different status in the Content Element and what does each status mean?]]></title> 
				<category>Content.cfm</category>
				<category>103_page</category>
				
				<description><![CDATA[There are five different status assignments:

1. Published: the version that currently appears on your site
2. Approved: versions that have been approved to be published
3. Approved & Scheduled: versions that have been approved and a time has been set for them to be automatically published
4. Rejected: versions that have been rejected
5. Pending: versions that are currently in progress or are waiting for approval]]></description> 
				<pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2007 02:57:54 EDT</pubDate> 
				<guid>100046_Core_Tip</guid>
			</item> 
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Why does my content sometimes look different after I paste it from MS Word?]]></title> 
				<category>Content.cfm</category>
				<category>Sockets.cfm</category>
				<category>103_page</category>
				<category>109_contentobject</category>
				
				<description><![CDATA[MS Word sometimes has hidden HTML tags that are not visible until you paste the content into a HTML editor (the WYSIWYG is an HTML editor).  

In the WYSIWYG use the "Paste from Word" icon (on the top row the blue "W" in front of the clip board).  When clicked, this button opens a small window with a text field where you will paste your content.  It is critical that you use this utility to avoid pasting in hidden HTML tags that may cause undesirable results in the display of your content.]]></description> 
				<pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2007 02:56:13 EDT</pubDate> 
				<guid>100047_Core_Tip</guid>
			</item> 
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Changing Navigation]]></title> 
				<category>Site.cfm</category>
				
				<description><![CDATA[Navigation items can link to several things: pages built with the page tool, database records for registered sockets, or custom/external urls. The Navigation Manager allows you to select, edit and re-order navigation items.]]></description> 
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2007 11:18:37 EDT</pubDate> 
				<guid>100008_Core_Tip</guid>
			</item> 
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Data Driven Navigation]]></title> 
				<category>Developer.cfm</category>
				
				<description><![CDATA[To quickly allow access to tool records for navigation, when creating a new socket, select the 'Records are Navigable' option. In conjunction with  a registered display handler (data driven display) this will allow navigation items to point to these records as the navigation address.]]></description> 
				<pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2007 03:02:54 EDT</pubDate> 
				<guid>100010_Core_Tip</guid>
			</item> 
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Switch socket data listing view (HTML/Flex CF 7 only).]]></title> 
				<category>Developer.cfm</category>
				<category>116_toolbuilder</category>
				
				<description><![CDATA[The listing view for data in most sockets can be displayed as either an HTML table, or as a Flex data grid. The view is changed by altering the form type (1st field when creating/editing a socket) from BoomSocket Admin (Custom/Core) to BoomSocket Admin (Flex). CF version 7.0.2+]]></description> 
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2007 02:36:42 EDT</pubDate> 
				<guid>100012_Core_Tip</guid>
			</item> 
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Socket/Tool Permissions]]></title> 
				<category>Admin.cfm</category>
				<category>106_Users</category>
				
				<description><![CDATA[Access to all the tools in BoomSocket are managed on a per user basis. When creating/editing users, one of the last steps is to set permissions for the user. Granting or denying permissions drive what the user will be able to access within BoomSocket.]]></description> 
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 05:00:57 EDT</pubDate> 
				<guid>100013_Core_Tip</guid>
			</item> 
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Fast Static Content]]></title> 
				<category>Content.cfm</category>
				<category>109_contentobject</category>
				
				<description><![CDATA[Content Elements are a great way to get data displayed fast and easy when that data doesn't change that often.]]></description> 
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2007 11:23:30 EDT</pubDate> 
				<guid>100014_Core_Tip</guid>
			</item> 
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Include Site meta not always a good thing]]></title> 
				<category>Content.cfm</category>
				<category>113_meta</category>
				
				<description><![CDATA[Many search engines frown on pages using the exact same keywords as other pages. So while it's tempting to "Include Site Meta" or 'Include Section Meta" on each page keep in mind that this might cause more harm then good.]]></description> 
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2007 11:24:23 EDT</pubDate> 
				<guid>100016_Core_Tip</guid>
			</item> 
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Fast Pages]]></title> 
				<category>Site.cfm</category>
				<category>103_page</category>
				
				<description><![CDATA[Don't forget that the page tool allows you to create content elements and have them automatically assigned to that page. This can lead to some very rapid development!]]></description> 
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2007 11:25:45 EDT</pubDate> 
				<guid>100018_Core_Tip</guid>
			</item> 
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Supervise Me]]></title> 
				<category>Admin.cfm</category>
				<category>118_SupervisorRelationship</category>
				
				<description><![CDATA[Supervisor relationships are a great way to manage your users and also keep the right people editing and publishing content. Note that supervisor oversight only applies to sockets that use Versioning.]]></description> 
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2007 11:26:48 EDT</pubDate> 
				<guid>100020_Core_Tip</guid>
			</item>
			</channel>
		</rss> 
